[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "During the Roman Empire, the Praetorians were the select few men who secretly carried out the desires of the emperor.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who were the feuding enemies of the McCoys?", "correct_answer": "Hat fields", "incorrect_answers": ["Earps", "Harrisons", "Daltons"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is not a type of conic section?", "correct_answer": "Ray", "incorrect_answers": ["Hyperbola", "Circle", "Parabola"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which of these areas is stretching the neck with neck rings practiced?", "correct_answer": "Africa and Asia", "incorrect_answers": ["Australia", "North America", "Africa and South America"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "To what perfume category do vanilla fragrances belong according to the modern classification of scents?", "correct_answer": "Gourmand", "incorrect_answers": ["Ozonic", "Aquatic", "Fruity"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In The Aristocats, after a big fight the butler is kicked into a trunk and locked inside. Where is the trunk going to be sent to?", "correct_answer": "Timbuktu", "incorrect_answers": ["New York", "Hollywood", "Australia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In square miles, what is the largest country in the world?", "correct_answer": "Russia", "incorrect_answers": ["Peoples Republic of China", "United States", "Canada"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The nose is an amazing piece of the human body.  Every flower or food gives off odor molecules that your nose picks up and your brain translates. How many smells can your brain recognize?", "correct_answer": "10,000", "incorrect_answers": ["5,000", "15,000", "20,000"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "It was proven that Thylacines killed some sheep in 1957.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who plays the Comedian in the film adaption of Watchmen?", "correct_answer": "Jefferey Blake Morgan", "incorrect_answers": ["Ralph Maggio", "Robert Downey Junior", "David Dean Walters"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Forrest Gump soundtrack was hugely popular, selling over 12 million copies. Which song/artist was not on the Forrest Gump soundtrack?", "correct_answer": "Satisfaction by The Rolling Stones", "incorrect_answers": ["Break on Through (To the Other Side) by The Doors", "California Dreamin by The Mamas and the Pappas", "Fortunate Son by CCR"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where is the southernmost point in all 50 states?", "correct_answer": "Hawaii", "incorrect_answers": ["Texas", "Florida", "California"]}]